alwadi-alakhdar.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy | Al Wadi Al Akhdar

By : | | On : August 27, 2015 | Category : 

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Al Wadi Al Akhdar and/or the website.  
The personal information we collect helps us develop and improve our products, services and advertising. We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis and research.  
We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling the abovementioned purposes, other purposes specified by us before or at the time of collecting personal information and other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate or if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm, financial loss, injury to or interference with our rights or property or the rights or property of our users or others, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.  
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.  
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means.  
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

To the extent possible, we will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. However, we cannot ensure that our level of security meets or exceeds any specific standards. No Internet transmission is 100% secure or error-free, nor is stored data free from vulnerabilities. We cannot guarantee the security of our websites, databases or services, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

We are not responsible for the actions of third parties.

We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

Al Wadi Al Akhdar and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistently with this Privacy Policy. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale, we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.
